Art Collins Collection ARC.0001
Library and Archives
Art Collins Papers
Bulk, 1986-2004
1959-2005 and undated
ARC.0001
Library and Archives
55.92 Linear feet
The papers of Art Collins span the years 1959 to 2005, with the bulk of the papers dating between 1986 and 2004. The collection provides rich documentation of Collins’ role as an artist manager. The documents pertain to the careers of the artists Collins managed, with Iggy Pop as the primary focus of the collection but including other artists like the Rolling Stones and Marianne Faithful. The legal papers consist of song licensing contracts, tour information, album release information, royalty contracts and statements, and press releases. Other material related to Collins’ clients includes correspondence, newspaper and periodical clippings, and audiovisual and printed material. The collection also contains audiovisual and printed materials from Collins’ personal music collection. These items span a vast range of rock groups (including John Lennon) and consist of periodicals, newspapers, books, sheet music, video tapes, audiocassettes, DVDs, 45 RPM records, and ¾” videocassettes. Collins’ papers provide documentation on the impact of clients on the history of rock music—specifically that of Iggy Pop on punk rock— and a behind-the-scenes look at being an artist and manager in the rock music industry.
Collins, Art, 1953-2005
Separated Materials
Books, sheet music books, 45 RPM vinyl records, and DVDs, as well as some audiotapes, videotapes, and periodicals have been transferred to the library collection. Please search for the "Art Collins Papers" in the library catalog for a list of donated titles.
Biography
Biography
1975 Joined Atlantic Records’ promotion department
1977 Joined Rolling Stone Records
1982 Founded Art Collins Management in New York City
1985 Became Iggy Pop’s manager
1989 Married Nikki
2005 July 27 Died of cardiac arrhythmia
Art Collins started his career in the music business in 1975 working in Atlantic Records’ promotion department. He joined Rolling Stones Records in 1977 and later became president of the company. In 1982, Collins left Rolling Stone Records and turned his attention to artist management, founding Art Collins Management in New York City. His clients included Joe Jackson, Marianne Faithful, Marshall Crenshaw, and Iggy Pop, whom Collins managed for over twenty years.
Sources
“Longtime Iggy Pop Manager Dies Suddenly.” Billboard. July 31, 2005. http://www.iggypop.org/artcollins.html.
Tomcho, Sandy. “Arthur Collins, Manager of Musicians Dies at 52.” Times Herald-Record. http://www.iggypop.org/artcollins.html.
Provenance
The Art Collins Papers was received by the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame Foundation, Inc. as a gift from Nikki Collins on December 30, 2006. The Rock and Roll Hall of Fame Foundation, Inc. transferred the collection to the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum, Inc. on March 31, 2011.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Patrons must sign the Acknowledgment of Legal Responsibility and Privacy Rights form before using this collection. Some of the audiovisual materials in the collection are on defunct media formats and, therefore, are RESTRICTED. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
Collins, Nikki; Faithfull, Marianne; Jagger, Mick; Lennon, John, 1940-1980; Pop, Iggy, 1947-; Rolling Stones; 45 RPM records.; Audiocassettes.; Books.; DVD--Video discs.; Music supervision.; Newspapers.; Periodicals.; Punk rock music.; Punk rock musicians--Management.; Rock groups--Management.; Rock music--United States.; Rock music--Writing and publishing.; Sheet music.; Video tapes.; ¾ inch videocassettes.
- Series I: Iggy Pop Legal Papers, 1995-2004 and undated
  Scope and Contents note
  Contains documents pertaining to Iggy Pop’s career, including song licensing, tour information, merchandising agreements, professional correspondence, royalty statements, and press information. The folders are arranged chronologically.
  - "Naughty Little Doggie" audiocassette (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Passenger" Japanese documentary use (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - No. 1 Drive (CD) (Passenger/ Poly UK) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Maverick Records: Vol. 2 "Passenger" use (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Maverick Records: Vol. 3 "Lust" use (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Candy" (Bug) / radio ad (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Doctor Music festival letter (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Freaks of Nature sampler CD (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Frank Rynne correspondence (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The Rutles (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - NY Times article (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Niagara Niagara (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 8 Days with Lester (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Rock Wives (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Long View Farm (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Mesa Boogie amps (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - DDB Needham (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Nick Tesco correspondence (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - New Yorker Magazine (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Virgin Best of 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Virgin Canada (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Pulp Magazine (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Skydog Royalties (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Lion's Pride CD (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - "Wild Wild Thing" / Tank Girl (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Edgefest / Minnesota (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Toronto Readbook (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Carolton Sandercock correspondence (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - "To Belong" video day sheet (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Zermati script (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - I Want My MTV / "Real Wild Child" (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Betsy Alexander correspondence (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Esquire request (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Flat Iron press (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Raw Power information (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Live reviews (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Glass Blowers Ball (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Garage Bands (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Road Stories book (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - ULI Heckman photograph (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Jimmy MAC / N.O. (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Mid Price request (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Nagase (Japan) (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Virgin VIP list (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - A&M royalties (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - MTV release – RHCP (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Rhino records compilation (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Live 105 / Top 105 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Bill German correspondence (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Pussy Walk sleeve (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Michael Oliveras resume - Bubbles (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Nagase / M. Ando (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Ardent Studios (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Gary Lucas stuff (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Complete music (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Slayer / Dog (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Joel Reiff Lighting (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Tour Managers CD (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Cliff Jones book (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Atolladero (Box 1, Box 60)
  - Thom Wilson producer (Box 1, Box 61)
  - Jimi Hendrix foundation (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Press clips (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Barb Wire movie (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Virgin International presentation (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Ogilvy & Mather (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Roskilde 25th anniversary (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Frank Rynne correspondence (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Aftra '95 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Trident Music (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Shure microphones (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Pagan fun wear (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Frank Kozik correspondence (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Tour managers (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Roadies (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Absolute Vodka (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Aftra Iggy (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Musicians (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Mick Rock (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Prince's Trust UK (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Kiss the Blood (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Complete Music series (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - WXRT "1969" CD Use (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - "Lust For Life" Scottish Police use (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Town Called Malice / Lust loop use (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Sagmeister CD cover (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Doddigitech pedals (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Joyce Green hospital (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Bug Music publication (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Siberia release (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Point Music (Brian Jones) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Amy Elliot script (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Shure / Billboard (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Doggie marketing (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ben Edmonds / Rhino (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Music Express (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Crow (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Boogie Boy (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chris Cuffaro correspondence (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Wendy Henry contract (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Rock for Choice (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The Crow publicity (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Album artwork info (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - "Lust for Life" DDB Needham (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Tour Bus leasing (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Brett O'Brien (S.O. Pro) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Tim Pope correspondence (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bomp Records (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Harvard Gig (MF) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Brion Gyson / Iggy Piece (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Muscle Shoals Studios (Alabama) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Tom Waits / Dave Mcgee correspondence (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Sister Midnight / HBO special documentary (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Adventures of Pete and Pete contract (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Mike's management producers (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Barb Wire correspondence (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - RJ Smith Halloween pack (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Marsha Vlasic / William Morris (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Details Magazine / Max's Kansas City special (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Sandra Marsh management (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Julie Brown(MAP) (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Passenger Munich / student film festival (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Perri Entertainment (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Sleeping on the Sun press kit (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Leos Caras letter (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Virgin International label copy (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - The Floating Men group (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Creative Hands (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Doggie artwork (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Andrew Burns / Guitar Tech (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Sparks album (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Bosnia thing (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Dresden idea (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Cellular One (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Iggy Pop and Johnny Deep interview (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Wofford Denius "Ed Hammell" (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Jampac / Krist Novoselic (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Rock and Roll Hall of Fame Concert / benefit album (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Potadam, Berlin (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Elizabeth Arden correspondence (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Janna Glasser correspondence (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - New Groups (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Newsweek / Time Out magazines (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - SXSW convention (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - "China Girl" Danish compilation (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - APA Drug Awareness / UK (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Milestones / UK (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Swietliki Fireflies / Polish rock group (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - John Giddings Summer 1996 dates (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Sidedoor Johnnies (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Kenickie band (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - PB High School parents night (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Pearl Show (WBTV) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Suddenly Susan licensing request (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Dimitri Erlich correspondence (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Eric Benson correspondence (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - The Band Concert / Harvest festival (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Matsuda show (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Virgin Germany interview disk (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Escape from Wonderful Life (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Anarchy TV, movie (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Dino Stamaopolous correspondence (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Magazine contract (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Music Cares fund (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Estate of Howard Tose (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Peace University, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Copyright renewal (Bug) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - "Cold Metal" Italian movie (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Rita Mitsouko / Codikow & Carroll (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Life on Mars (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Microsoft CD Rom request (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Brockum tax certificate (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Henry McGroggan correspondence (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Jens Bidstruf (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Sonic Net (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Doggie reviews (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Arena magazine (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - John Diddings (Ramones) (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Highland Telephone (office) (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Europe tour 1996 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Summer 1997 tour dates (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - French tour (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Mexico tour (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Australian tour (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Edge Fest Minneapolis (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Iggy / Doggie notes (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - US tour, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - "Lust for Life" UK Sunday Times (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "The Passenger" Made in Germany documentary (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Planet Hollywood (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Hear Charity CD (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Incommunicado book publishers (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Resumes (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Dod electronic (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - "Platinum" use (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bob Burt baseball collection (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Michael Tipton / Metallica (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Final Rinse / script letter (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Richard Farrell / script letter (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Trainspotting II (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Stella Miller / Charles Lyonheart (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Virgin International updates (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 1997 Motion Pix almanac (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - New Album (Outta My Head) production information (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Mean Fiddler letter (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Japan tour 1996 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - "Gimme Danger" Velvet Goldmine (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Barry Davey wire transfer (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Tuborg beer (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - "Lust for Life" British awards (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Virgin "Best Of.." release (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Bob Dole / Trainspotting (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - "Ride the Fucking Wild" (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Bowie turns 50 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - The Crow / Alain Lahana (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Jan Hause / Punk Hole of Fame (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Parliament Funkadelic documentary (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Bob Walker speaker list (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Time Zones Italy (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Mark Terry / Trainspotting (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - South Bank Show documentaries (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - German Vogue picture (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Eric Schermerhorn / Mesa Boogie (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - David Mcgee correspondence (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - "Gimme Danger" lead sheet (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Milestones (UK) (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Doug Aiken (Howard Satellite Films) (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Janet Grey / Personal Hell (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Anarchy TV (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - King Biscuit Flower Hour CD (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Pepsi World tour (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Eco Quix (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Dan Rose video (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Rock Walk info (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - JSR merchandising (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Rolling Stone International Virgin memo (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Hard Core logo (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Alex & Levi demos (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Inger Lorre demos (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Bug Music (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Times Herald review (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - "Real Wild Child" Virgin Best of… (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Hustler magazine (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Ray Manzarek audio (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Nils Cigarette ad (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Andrew Solt Productions / History of Rock and Roll (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Federal Express commercial invoices (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Federal Express domestic (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - New groups (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Federal Express international (letter) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Carl Perkins Death / obituary and account (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Dave Barry and Mick Jagger / January 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Virgin web site (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Dimitri Erlich correspondence (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - January - June 1995 statement / Virgin royalties (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Buzzard Song / Porgy and Bess (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Australia 1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Rolling Stones MSG ticket (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Pen Pal Group / Karen Wilshinsky (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Stisism / Chris Curlyo (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - The Village Gate (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - AIDS prevention (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Art Collins and Nikki correspondence (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Virgin statement, December 1997 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Porno / Moby (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - 200 Cigarettes / Courtney Love (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Atlanta date (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Germany / March 1998 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Nancy Berry: Wall Street Journal story (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Italian Vogue wardrobe shoot (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Psycho Backho comic book (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Jim DeRogatis: Lester Bangs book (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - The Simpsons (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - EMI Music publications (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Rollins catalog (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Dr. Marvin Corn (Eyes) (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Elektra royalty statement (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Terry Southern obituary (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Andy McCoy (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Greg Anici / singer-songwriter (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Iggy updates, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Hustler photograph (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Elle Decoration / Iggy's apartment (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Shure / Iggy HW distribution catalog (UK) (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Tower Argentina (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - House of Blues Summer of Love (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Grand Funk reunion (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - The Byrds: Sony legacy kit (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - "Lust for Life" Something for the Weekend (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Magnetic Poetry / Esquire magazine (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Scott Litt correspondence (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Julie Ana Klausner loyalty press (Sex Thing) (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Zebra Stripes / Richard Farrell (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Maureen Mahon / Total Mayhem productions (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Voice of America radio (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Roman Empire / Alexandria productions (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - VH1: 100 Greatest Artists of Rock and Roll (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Pam Turbo: HCDC software (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Rollins Publications / royalty statements (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - "Lust for Life" History of Punk Vol. 2 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - "Lust for Life" Best Indie LP's Ever (UK) (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Made in Germany Video use (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - "Lust for Life" Saturday Night Oil (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Shure Microphone ads, September 1997 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Gary Grimshaw posters, 1988 to 1997 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Popular History Company: Canadian TV release (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Rugrats Movie contract (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Juliana Plotkin resume (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - BAM/MF bill for car (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Sam Nole correspondence (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Pat Hearn fund (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Martin Baker documentaries (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Bono/U2 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Doctor Chance: 2 Songs (French) (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Nude and Rude report (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Bill German (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Virgin International plan, Nude and Rude (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - "Lust for Life" DVD sampler (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - IRA Robbins: MJA broadcasting (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Moviewatch: "Lust for Life" (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Resumes (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Stooge – Staffe (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Passengers - UK short film (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - "Passenger" Toyota ad (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Suchi's book (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Brockum merchandise (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Dean Kulpers / Raygun (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Nude and Rude report (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Lyric Book(Art) (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Total Mayhem core script (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - China Girl "Covers" (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Iggy/Larry letters (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - A&M royalty sheet (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - James Williamson correspondence (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Nude and Rude report (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - David Arnold video thing (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Greg Shaw, 1997 Bomp (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Incommunicado publishers (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Man on the Moon / K. Lafferty (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Royalty Records, Iggy tribute (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Detroit Tigers (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Russia tour date (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - "Raw Power" label/copy (Bug Music) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - JSR merchandising (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Icon magazine (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Virgin International promo (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Allen Ginsburg trust 1997 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - King Biscuit Flower Hour channel (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Jane Ratcliff Hour / Detroit (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Red Hot Organization, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - "Success" Great Expectation (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Rattlz CD (Jim Dunbar) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - How to file a copyright (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - We Like Monster Men CD (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - The Outer Reefs Treatment (Linden Travel) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Mark Romanek / contents magazine (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Iggy Pop webpage (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Chris Cufaro postcards (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Trainspotting II (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Technic ad request (Solo) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Bill Graham letters (Stones) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - China Girl /Feeling" Chile request (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - "Gimme Danger'' Whatever Film (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - School of the Arts / Rochester (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - David Bowie stock (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Noreen Byatt thank you note (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Morcheeba group (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Razor and Tie catalog (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - L.A. Without a Map script letter (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Francois Hardy / French standards (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Sexpod, Don Kaye (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Firecracker Alternative Book Awards / Rollins Publications (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Rock for Choice, August 1997 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - South Bank Show / Susan Shaw, August 1997 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Dr. Jim Dwyer / NJ RX (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Doug Klozzner / Dum Dum Boys (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Liz Ashton letter (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Bryant Burns correspondence (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - College Music Journal, 1997 brochure (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Spunk bank kit (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Larry Busacca / photographer (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Roar Tour premium CD (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - "China Girl" In Concert (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Progressive auto insurance (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Bryan Barr / Psycho letter, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Travis auto insurance (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Poetry Project 1997 / "Some of the Dharma" (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Utah Saints (ECHO Label) (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Suzi Scott "Search and Destroy" sample (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Virgin statement, January to June 1997 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Press clips (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Bug Music statement, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Mick Rock Benefit (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Press clips (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Devil Deer (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Girls Travel (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Family portrait (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - "China Girl" Cupid (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - MTV Biorhythm “Winners and Losers” (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - "Monster Man" French restaurant (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - "Lust for Life" Drew Carey Show (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Danny Clinch photograph (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Chelmsford UK (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Tim McGregor Falls Festival communication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Slovakian UK date (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Call sheets (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - SCL Punk / Bug (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - MVO US dates, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Date sheet, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Itineraries (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Lava Lamp information (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Music Express limousine (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Itineraries (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Leeds UK (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Arte documentary (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Bizarre festival, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Skelleftta Festival Sweden (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Crossing Border Festival, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Lollipop Festival Sweden, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Bizarre Festival (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Spain " Esparrago" Festival (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Portugal, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - G. Pollen obituary (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Bug statement (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Rugrats final agreement file copy (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Summer of Sam (Spike Lee Movie) (Box 7, Folder 30)